

Robert Cristian Popesc u

Date of birth: 05/12/1996
Nationality: Romanian

Gender: Male

CONTACT

- 077042 Chiajna, Romania (Home)
- robert.popescu9612@gmail.com
- (+40) 762231012
- https://rob3rt96.github.io/
- https://github.com/rob3rt96
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/robert-cristian-popescu/
- https://wa.me/40762231012 (W hatsapp)

ABOUT ME

I am an engineer and a self-taught software developer, interested in working on projects made with Java and Spring in Backend Development, or even with Javascript. During the time after I graduated, I learned by completing some courses and reading a few programming books.

I am pursuing to gain real experience during an internship or even in a Junior position.

DIGITAL SKILLS

BACK-END

Java 17 | Bazele programării Java | Familiar with the concept of Unit-test using JUnit | Spring | REST services | SQL / No SQL Databases

FRONT-END

Mocha | Limbaje de Programare: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript | Frontend developer - HTML5, CSS, JS | React.js (începător)

OFFICE SUITE

Microsoft Office | Microsoft Excel | Navigare Internet

WORK EXPERIENCE

04/2022 - 02/2023 Bucuresti, Romania

Learning & Personal projects in Javascript/React codecademy. com

- 1. Fundamentals of HTML: Elements, Tables, Semantic HTML
- 2. **Fundamentals of CSS**: Selectors and visual rules, Typography, Color Theory, Accessibility
- 3. **Mastering the following**: CSS Flexbox, CSS Grid, Media Queries, CSS Transitions, and Animations
- 4. **Javascript**: Functions, Scope, Variables, and Data Types, Objects, Arrays, Iterators
- 5. Javascript: Classes, Modules, Error Handling, Promises, Async/Await
- Javascript Testing: TDD with Mocha + Chai, Code coverage, Mocking, Spies
- 7. **ReactJS**: JSX, Virtual DOM, Components, Hooks, Redux, react-redux, reduxjs@toolkit

09/2021 - 03/2022 Bucuresti, Romania

Junior Java Developer Atos IT Solutions and Services

I studied different fields of software development like:

- 1. Java SE 11
- 2. MySQL
- 3. Agile Methodologies (Scrum, Kanban, etc.)
- 4. Linux Essentials

11/2019 - 02/2021 Bucuresti, Romania

Mobile Trail Planner Huawei

- Site Integration (2G, 3G, 4G) and the extension of network elements in connection with the radio rollout measures.
- Preparation of planning data on request and documentation in the relevant databases (Cramer Mobile/ANN, Cramer 6).
- Ensuring the quality of data provided (control of the network parameters, according to the received instruction).
- Interacting with internal technical areas (Vodafone Germany and Vodafone Group) for Mobile Trail Planning.
- Basic IP knowledge: SDH, PDH, Routing, TCP/IP, PPP&PPPoe Protocols, Ethernet

Address Str. Barbu Văcărescu 301, București 077190, Bucuresti, Romania

09/2019 - 11/2019 Bucuresti, Romania

C# Software Developer Spectra Computers Int'l

- Troubleshooting IT systems
 - · Working in C#
 - Working with Microsoft Sharepoint Server

Address Bucuresti, Romania

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

10/2020 - CURRENT

Master's degree University POLITEHNICA of Bucharest

Website https://upb.ro/en/ | Field of study Database Administration

09/2015 - 07/2019 Bucuresti, Romania

Bachelor of Engineering - BE University POLITEHNICA of Bucharest

Faculty of Industrial Engineering and Robotics, Robotics Specialization

Address Bucuresti, Romania | Website https://upb.ro/en/ | Field of study Robotics

09/2011 - 06/2015 Bolintin-Vale, Romania

Baccalaureate Degree "Dimitrie Bolintineanu" Technological High School

Address Bolintin-Vale, Romania | Website https://liceubolintin.com/

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Romanian

Other language(s):

English

Listening Reading Spoken production **Spoken interaction** Writing C1 C1R2 R2 R2

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Communication and interpersonal skills

- Teamwork: I have the experience of teamwork acquired while working with colleagues in my last jobs.
- Focusing on an activity until its successful completion.
- · Promptness in solving work tasks.

Certifications

04/2022 - 02/2023

Front-End Engineer Career Path - Codecademy

- Fundamentals of HTML: Elements, Tables, Semantic HTML
- Fundamentals of CSS: Selectors and visual rules, Typography, Color

Theory, Accessibility

Mastering the following: CSS Flexbox, CSS Grid, Media Queries, CSS Transitions, and Animations

- Javascript: Functions, Scope, Variables, and Data Types, Objects, Arrays, Iterators
- Javascript: Classes, Modules, Error Handling, Promises, Async/Await
- Javascript Testing: TDD with Mocha + Chai, Code coverage, Mocking,
- ReactJS: JSX, Virtual DOM, Components, Hooks, Redux, react-redux, reduxjs@toolkit

Link https://www.codecademy.com/profiles/robert9612/certificates/5f85dd867b67b60014ac9ea3

04/2021 - 06/2021

Java Programming II

University of Helsinki Programming Course

Link https://certificates.mooc.fi/validate/axhmlbu4ta

02/2021 - 04/2021

Java Programming I

University of Helsinki Programming Course

Link https://certificates.mooc.fi/validate/axhmlbu4ta

Certifications

C Fundamentals (Issued May 2018) - BIT Academy Credential ID 0000006494

Driving Licence

Driving Licence: AM

